{
  "letters": {
    "groups": [
      {
        "name": "aeiou",
        "items": [
          {
            "question": "あ",
            "answer": "a"
          },
          {
            "question": "い",
            "answer": "i"
          },
          {
            "question": "う",
            "answer": "u"
          },
          {
            "question": "え",
            "answer": "e"
          },
          {
            "question": "お",
            "answer": "o"
          },
          {
            "question": "か",
            "answer": "ki"
          },
          {
            "question": "き",
            "answer": "ki"
          },
          {
            "question": "く",
            "answer": "ku"
          },
          {
            "question": "け",
            "answer": "ke"
          },
          {
            "question": "こ",
            "answer": "ko"
          },
          {
            "question": "さ",
            "answer": "sa"
          },
          {
            "question": "し",
            "answer": "sì"
          },
          {
            "question": "す",
            "answer": "su"
          },
          {
            "question": "せ",
            "answer": "se"
          },
          {
            "question": "そ",
            "answer": "so"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}